wefollow.com 2015-06-24

# Privacy : Wefollow : Discover prominent people

### Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the wefollow.com and Jeff Hodsdon, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Wefollow include wefollow.com and Jeff Hodsdon, LLC. The Wefollow website is a Social metrics and interest directory site. By using the Wefollow website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

Wefollow may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Wefollow. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Wefollow website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Wefollow's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Wefollow encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Wefollow so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Wefollow is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Wefollow website.

#### Use of your Personal Information

Wefollow collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Wefollow may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Wefollow and its affiliates. Wefollow may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Wefollow does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Wefollow may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Wefollow, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Wefollow will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Jeff Hodsdon, LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Jeff Hodsdon, LLC; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Wefollow, or the public.

#### Use of Cookies

The Wefollow website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Wefollow pages, or register with Wefollow site or services, a cookie helps Wefollow to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Wefollow website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Wefollow features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Wefollow services or websites you visit.

#### Security of your Personal Information

Wefollow secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

#### Children Under Thirteen

Wefollow does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Disconnecting your Wefollow Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Wefollow account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR WEFOLLOW ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may go to their profiles and when logged in they my toggle (connect or disconnect) any third party connections.

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Wefollow by contacting us here:

\- Email: [help@about.me](mailto:help@about.me)

#### Changes to this Statement

Wefollow will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Wefollow encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Wefollow is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

Wefollow welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Wefollow has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Wefollow at:

    Jeff Hodsdon, LLC
    533 E 5th St #20
    New York, New York 10009
    Email Address: jeff@wefollow.com
    Telephone number: 4152699611
